<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TorunTourGuideApp</string>

       <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="museum_title_1">Toruń Regional Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_content_1">
        Located in the Town Hall of Toruń,
        is one of the oldest and largest museums in Poland.
        Exhibitions:
        Gallery of Gothic Art.
        Old Toruń - 1233-1793. History, art and crafts.
        Royal Room - The set of the portraits of Polish monarchs.
        Gallery of Polish Painting from the end of 18th century to circ. 1939.
    </string>


    <string name="museum_title_2">Copernicus House</string>
    <string name="museum_content_2">
        Nicolaus Copernicus was a Renaissance-era mathematician and astronomer who formulated a
        model of the universe that placed the Sun rather than the Earth at the center of the universe.
        There is no doubt that Nicolaus Copernicus was born in Toruń !!
        The exhibition "Nicolaus Copernicus - the life and work"
    </string>

    <string name="museum_title_3">Ethnographic Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_content_3">
        The Museum basic task is accumulating, scientific working out, storage, protection, conservation
        and making goods of culture available for people. Exhibitions: "Secrets of everyday life."
Folk culture and related border issues from Kujawy to the Baltic Sea (1850-1950)
    </string>

    <string name="museum_title_4">Planetarium</string>

    <string name="museum_content_4">The Planetarium in Torun was opened in February, 1994 and is very popular with school groups,
        families with children and tourists. It is located in a historical tank of the old municipal gasworks in the Old Town.
The Planetarium offers astronomical shows in the screening room under the dome and two interactive exhibitions: MARS#17 Base and Geodium.</string>

    <string name="museum_title_5">CENTRE OF CONTEMPORARY ART</string>

    <string name="museum_content_5">
        CoCA in Torun, even if young, already profiled itself like an institution that puts emphasis on concepts of “being contemporary” and “being international”.
        It’s interdisciplinary character and it’s openness towards most innovative and “cutting edge” researches in variety of expressive media guarantees it’s active
        and dynamic role within regional and national cultural context, and underlines it’s strong potential in a dialogue with other contemporary art institutions operating world-wide.

    </string>


    <!-- DainerData -->
    <string name="diner_title_1">Manekin</string>
    <string name="diner_content_1">
        Restaurant specialty:\nSavoury Pancakes, Oven-baked Pancakes with Cheese, Spelt Pancakes...\nRynek Staromiejski 16, Wysoka 5
    </string>

    <string name="diner_title_2">Luizjana</string>
    <string name="diner_content_2">
        Restaurant specialty:\nAmerican, Cajun and Louisiana Creole cuisine.\nMostowa 10/1

    </string>
    <string name="diner_title_3">Royal India</string>
    <string name="diner_content_3">
        Restaurant specialty:\nIndian and Asian cuisine.\nProsta 19

    </string>
    <string name="diner_title_4">Pasta i Basta</string>
    <string name="diner_content_4">
        Restaurant specialty:\nItalian cuisine.\nRynek Staromiejski 10

    </string>
    <string name="diner_title_5">Pierogarnia Pod Blaszanym Kotem</string>
    <string name="diner_content_5">
        Restaurant specialty:\nPolish Dumplings.\nRynek Staromiejski 8

    </string>

    <!-- EventData -->
    <string name="event_title_1">Bella Skyway Festival</string>
    <string name="event_content_1">
        The festival that consists of installations made primarily of light.
        Luminous works of art dispersed in various places of the city, projections
        and interactive presentations are prepared by an international group of artists
        especially for the presentation in Toruń. Buildings and squares change their shapes
        and gain a new, previously unknown face thanks to illuminations and projections.
    </string>

    <string name="event_title_2">International Film Festival Tofifest</string>
    <string name="event_content_2">
        The International Film Festival "Tofifest" is a real fest for the cinema lovers.
        It is also one of the largest and the most interesting summer film events in Poland.
        The Tofifest is sometimes called "the Polish Sundance". Among titles displayed during the review,
        there are films awarded in Berlin, Cannes and Locarno, as well as promising debuts.

    </string>
    <string name="event_title_3">Special Concert in memory of Grzegorz Ciechowski.</string>
    <string name="event_content_3">
        Each year in December, the Special Concert in memory of Grzegorz Ciechowski is being organised in the Od Nowa club.
        The invitation to attend the event is accepted by the greatest celebrities of the Polish stage.
        We hosted, inter alia, Justyna Steczkowska, Kasia Nosowska and Hey, Tomek Lipiński, Maria Peszek, Muniek Staszczyk, Kazik Staszewski, the Mech band and many others.

    </string>
    <string name="event_title_4">Probaltica</string>
    <string name="event_content_4">
        The idea of the festival was created at the beginning of the 90s when Baltic countries were re-established.
        Then, it became clear how little people living in these countries know about the culture of their neighbours,
        despite the geographical proximity. The festival was intended to change this, therefore its subsequent editions include
        the need of presentation of the cultural heritage of all Baltic countries to the Polish audience.

    </string>

    <!-- DainerData -->
    <string name="night_title_1">Lizard King</string>
    <string name="night_content_1">
        The best music club in the city. Great concerts and standups. On Friday and Saturday a great place to dance.\nKopernika 8
    </string>

    <string name="night_title_2">Hipisówka</string>
    <string name="night_content_2">
        Great place for Jamsesion. You can meet here many musicians from Toruń bands, talk, play and spend an interesting evening.
        And to eat all the best PIZZA in the city at 4am.\nKopernika 10

    </string>
    <string name="night_title_3">Zezowate Szczęście</string>
    <string name="night_content_3">
        A magical place from the borderline of sleep and waking. Good drinks and good music.
        I can meet the actors of Toruń's theater here.
        Conversations on many topics last until early morning.\nśw. Ducha 5

    </string>
    <string name="night_title_4">Tratwa</string>
    <string name="night_content_4">
        Pub located in a beautiful place. Summer garden among green trees and bushes.
        In the afternoon - friendly for animals and children (sand-pit, slides).\nFlisacza 7A

    </string>
    <string name="night_title_5">Kadr</string>
    <string name="night_content_5">
       Personnel invariably since 2004 is on the map of every Toruń student. A club housed in a medieval cellar is a tribute to the cinema and the stars of the silver screen.
        The atmosphere is built here by the decor - the walls are decorated with posters and photos, and film gadgets hang from the ceiling.\nZeglarska 5

    </string>


</resources>
